

Gökalp Giray

Frontend Developer

★ gokalpgiray.github.io/Portfolio/ **in** gokalpgiray **(**) GokalpGiray

₽ Profile

Hello. I wanted to embody my interest in software development, which has started in the last years of my university life, and turn it into my profession. I have chosen frontend development as a new career path for myself. For this purpose, I am still working hard. Using the work ethic and discipline I've gained from my work experience for many years, I am trying to become an expert in this field by constantly improving myself. You can check my work on my GitHub page.

Education

2015 – 2020	Bachelor's Degree, Survey Engineering, Çanakkale Onsekiz Mart University ⊘	Çanakkale, Turkey
2014 – 2015	English Preparation, School of Foreign Languages, Karadeniz Technical University ⊘	Trabzon, Turkey
2010 – 2014	High School, Math - Science, Fahreddin Kerim Gökay Anatolian High School	İstanbul, Turkey

Professional Experience

	•	
07/2021 - 09/2022	Survey Engineer, 3408/22 No'lu Lisanslı Harita Kadastro Mühendislik Bürosu	Istanbul, Turkey
02/2020 - 07/2021	Quality Control Specialist, <i>GKN Sinter İstanbul Metal San. ve Tic.A.Ş.</i>	Istanbul, Turkey
07/2019 - 01/2020	Travel Consultant, Capacity Jolly Tur	Istanbul, Turkey
12/2018 - 03/2019	Intern Survey Engineer, 1706/98 No'lu Lisanslı Harita Kadastro Mühendislik Bürosu	Çanakkale, Turkey
07/2017 – 09/2017	Intern Survey Engineer, Küçükçekmece Kadastro Birimi	Istanbul, Turkey

Projects

Gurme Şef 1974, The website I prepared for Gurme Şef 1974 *∂*

diyetisyenbuseakduman.com, The website I prepared for Expert Dietitian Buse Akduman ⊘

Disney+ Clone,

I cloned the Disney+ site as a demo. Don't forget to login to the site with your Google account;) ∂

Contacts App, I developed a simple contact app using React and Redux. *∂*

Breaking Bad App, Using React and Redux, I developed a simple application that contains the characters and words of the Breaking Bad series. \varnothing

ල ි

Skills

- React
 JavaScript
- HTML

CSS

- Bootstrap
- Redux

- Matlab
- git

Java

• MS Office

S Languages

සිං Familiar With

English (Intermediate)

Turkish (Native Language)

Agile

Scrum and Kanban

ලී

Interests

Basketball

I have been watching, playing, listening and following basketball for many years. Even though I can't watch the matches all the time, I somehow follow the leagues.

Formula 1

Especially in recent years, my interest in Formula 1, which I watched as a child, has flared up again. I try to follow it as closely as possible. Forza Ferrari!

Tennis

I've been watching and playing since I was a kid. This sport taught me to manage my ambition and patience.

战 References

Oğuz Özkeroğlu, Lead Developer, Ericsson Sweden oguz.ozkeroglu@ericsson.com, +46 72 300 50 80

<u>Serhat Akkuş</u>, *Software Lead* serhatakkus@gmail.com, +90 535 610 64 33

<u>Melek Pazarbaşı</u>, *Software Engineer*, ING Türkiye melekp30@gmail.com, +90 538 979 22 90

<u>Taha Furkan Tarakçı</u>, *Lead Developer*, Taksim Games tahatarakci34@gmail.com, +90 535 255 61 47

٥Ţ

Certificates

HTML5 and CSS3 Fundamentals ₽

Intermediate Frontend Web

<u>Development Path</u> *⊗*